Edward R. Murrow Papers MS025
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Memorabilia, 1906 -- 1967; MS025.006; 15.4 Linear Feet; 1 Artifact(s); 64 Digital Object(s)
  - Personal Items, 1906 -- 1965; MS025.006.004; 2.2 Linear Feet; 61 Digital Object(s)
    - Edward R. Murrow stands with an unidentified man in front of a television camera looking at an engineering model, 1957; MS025.006.004.002.00008.00030 (Box data_value_missing_05b4da3e50d85afd11acbf4f59fb3aa8)
      Television cameras; Engineering models; Murrow, Edward R.; CBS; International Harvester Company of America
    - Edward R. Murrow sits next to an engineering model with an unidentified man, 1957; MS025.006.004.002.00008.00031 (Box data_value_missing_05b4da3e50d85afd11acbf4f59fb3aa8)
      Engineering models; Factories; Designs and plans; Murrow, Edward R.; CBS; International Harvester Company of America
    - Edward R. Murrow and an unidentified man pose beside a podium showing medal for International Trucks - World's Most Complete Line 1907-1957, International Harvester Company, MS025.006.004.002.00008.00032 (Box data_value_missing_05b4da3e50d85afd11acbf4f59fb3aa8)
      Awards; Medals; Microphone; Murrow, Edward R.; CBS; International Harvester Company of America
    - Edward R. Murrow and an unidentified man seated at a desk with a U.S. map in the background, 1957; MS025.006.004.002.00008.00033 (Box data_value_missing_05b4da3e50d85afd11acbf4f59fb3aa8)
      United States; Maps; Murrow, Edward R.; CBS; International Harvester Company of America
    - Edward R. Murrow with John McCaffrey and four unidentified men, 1957; MS025.006.004.002.00008.00034 (Box data_value_missing_05b4da3e50d85afd11acbf4f59fb3aa8)
    - Three men (unidentified) seated in front of a chart showing truck growth and population growth, 1957; MS025.006.004.002.00008.00035 (Box data_value_missing_05b4da3e50d85afd11acbf4f59fb3aa8)
      --Statistics--Charts, diagrams, etc.; Trucks; CBS; International Harvester Company of America
    - Two men (unidentified), seated in front of a U.S. map, 1957; MS025.006.004.002.00008.00036 (Box data_value_missing_05b4da3e50d85afd11acbf4f59fb3aa8)
      United States; Maps; CBS; International Harvester Company of America
    - Edward R. Murrow on a television monitor, 1957; MS025.006.004.002.00008.00037 (Box data_value_missing_05b4da3e50d85afd11acbf4f59fb3aa8)
      Murrow, Edward R.; CBS; International Harvester Company of America
    - Edward R. Murrow with John McCaffrey on a television monitor, 1957; MS025.006.004.002.00008.00038 (Box data_value_missing_05b4da3e50d85afd11acbf4f59fb3aa8)
      Automobiles; Models (representations); Murrow, Edward R.; McCaffrey, John L.; CBS; International Harvester Company of America
    - John McCaffrey on a television monitor, 1957; MS025.006.004.002.00008.00039 (Box data_value_missing_05b4da3e50d85afd11acbf4f59fb3aa8)
      Automobiles; Models (representations); McCaffrey, John L.; CBS; International Harvester Company of America
    - Edward R. Murrow and an unidentified man on a television monitor, 1957; MS025.006.004.002.00008.00040 (Box data_value_missing_05b4da3e50d85afd11acbf4f59fb3aa8)
      Automobiles; Models (representations); Murrow, Edward R.; CBS; International Harvester Company of America
    - Edward R. Murrow and two unidentified men in front of a U.S. map on a television monitor, 1957; MS025.006.004.002.00008.00041 (Box data_value_missing_05b4da3e50d85afd11acbf4f59fb3aa8)
      United States; Maps; Engineering models; Murrow, Edward R.; CBS; International Harvester Company of America
    - Edward R. Murrow looks at text with an unidentified man, both standing in front of a chart, on a television monitor, 1957; MS025.006.004.002.00008.00042 (Box data_value_missing_05b4da3e50d85afd11acbf4f59fb3aa8)
      Statistics--Charts, diagrams, etc.; Murrow, Edward R.; CBS; International Harvester Company of America
    - Edward R. Murrow looks at a text with an unidentified man, both sitting in front of a chart, on a television monitor, 1957; MS025.006.004.002.00008.00043 (Box data_value_missing_05b4da3e50d85afd11acbf4f59fb3aa8)
    - Edward R. Murrow looks at an engineering model with an unidentified man, on a television monitor, 1957; MS025.006.004.002.00008.00044 (Box data_value_missing_05b4da3e50d85afd11acbf4f59fb3aa8)
    - Edward R. Murrow seated with an unidentified man, on a television monitor, 1957; MS025.006.004.002.00008.00045 (Box data_value_missing_05b4da3e50d85afd11acbf4f59fb3aa8)
    - Edward R. Murrow seated with an unidentified man, on a television monitor, 1957; MS025.006.004.002.00008.00046 (Box data_value_missing_05b4da3e50d85afd11acbf4f59fb3aa8)
    - An unidentified man posing next to a podium showing medal for International Trucks - World's Most Complete Line 1907-1957, International Harvester Company, on a television monitor, MS025.006.004.002.00008.00047 (Box data_value_missing_05b4da3e50d85afd11acbf4f59fb3aa8)
      Awards; CBS; International Harvester Company of America
    - A group of unidentified men standing on stage, 1957; MS025.006.004.002.00008.00048 (Box data_value_missing_05b4da3e50d85afd11acbf4f59fb3aa8)
      Executives; CBS; International Harvester Company of America
    - An automobile on stage, 1957; MS025.006.004.002.00008.00049 (Box data_value_missing_05b4da3e50d85afd11acbf4f59fb3aa8)
      Trucks; CBS; International Harvester Company of America
    - Edward R. Murrow waving, in front of an airplane, 1957; MS025.006.004.002.00008.00050 (Box data_value_missing_05b4da3e50d85afd11acbf4f59fb3aa8)
    - Appointment of Edward R. Murrow as Director of U.S. Information Agency, 1961; MS025.006.004.002.00009 (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
      Dimensions: 23"W x 20 1/4"H. Signed by President John F. Kennedy. This document was added to the box after 2005. Originally, the document was framed and displayed in the Murrrow Room. There is further information about the document in item record: MS025.006.001.00106. 39090015524776y.
    - Presidential Medal of Freedom Award, 1964; MS025.006.004.002.00010 (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
      Dimensions: 14 3/4W x 12"H. This document was added to the box after 2005. Originally, the document was framed and displayed in the Murrrow Room. There is further information about the document in item record: MS025.006.001.00107. 39090015524776y.
    - Images and Photographs of and owned by Edward R. Murrow, 1944 -- 1959; MS025.006.004.003.00001 (Box MS025 Shared 2)
    - Gladys Hall and Janet Murrow in Washington, D.C., 1944; MS025.006.004.003.00001.00001 (Box MS025 Shared 2)
    - US soldier (unidentified) receiving a medal, 1941 -- 1945; MS025.006.004.003.00001.00002 (Box MS025 Shared 2)
      Dates are an approximation.
      United States; Soldiers; Medals; World War, 1939-1945
    - Soldier (unidentified) pictured with a young girl and puppy, 1940 -- 1945; MS025.006.004.003.00001.00003 (Box MS025 Shared 2)
      Dates are approximation.
      Soldiers; Girls; Dogs; World War, 1939-1945
    - Military planes lined up on a runway, 1940 -- 1945; MS025.006.004.003.00001.00004 (Box MS025 Shared 2)
      Airplanes; World War, 1939-1945
    - Two airmen loading ammunition, 1940 -- 1945; MS025.006.004.003.00001.00005 (Box MS025 Shared 2)
      Airmen; Ammunition; Airplanes
    - 'BBC Television Service War Correspondents Return to Europe Ed Murrow' Edward R. Murrow publicity photograph for the BBC's "After the Battle" film series, 1959; MS025.006.004.003.00001.00006 (Box MS025 Shared 2)
      On back of photograph: "22.10.59 / BBC Television Service, War Correspondents Return to Europe. Ed Murrow, who since the war has made such an impact on American and British television, opens the BBC-tv film series AFTER THE BATTLE on Wednesday November 18th (9.30 p.m.) in which six well-known radio war correspondents return to the scenes of some of their most famous wartime despatches [sic.]. During this thiry minute film Murrow discusses the tense days of 1940-41 with the Foreign Secretary, Mr. Selwyn Lloyd, Mr. Frank Cousins and Professor D.W. Brogan." Credit: BBC Copyright Photograph, from BBC, Broadcasting House, London, W. 1.
      War correspondents; World War, 1939-1945; Murrow, Edward R.
    - Edward R. Murrow, Caricature by Horace Knight, 1955; MS025.006.004.003.00001.00007 (Box MS025 Shared 2)
      #45/256. Approximate year for photograph.
      Caricature; Murrow, Edward R.
    - Personal Identification Cards, Business Cards and Permits, 1936 -- 1944; MS025.006.004.003.00002 (Box MS025 Shared 2)
      Includes press passes, visitor passes, identification cards, identification card photographs, business cards. There are duplicates of business cards.
    - The Ministry of Information Press Pass, World War II, United Kingdom, 1939 -- 1945; MS025.006.004.003.00002.00001 (Box MS025 Shared 2)
      Approximate year for photograph.
      World War, 1939-1945; War correspondents; Identification cards; Murrow, Edward R.; CBS; Mirror, the
    - Edward R. Murrow, 1937 -- 1945; MS025.006.004.003.00002.00002 (Box MS025 Shared 2)
      Photograph likely removed from press pass or other identification card. Approximate year for photograph.
    - Edward R. Murrow, 1940; MS025.006.004.003.00002.00003 (Box MS025 Shared 2)
      Photograph used for identification cards, e.g. Republic Francaise Sauf-Conduit - Etranger 1940 and BBC Visitor's Pass 31.3. 1944. Duplicates exist.
      World War, 1939-1945; Identification cards; Murrow, Edward R.; CBS
    - Edward R. Murrow, 1940; MS025.006.004.003.00002.00004 (Box MS025 Shared 2)
      Photograph scanned from French identification papers, Republique Francaise Sauf-Conduit - Etranger.
    - Correspondence - CBS, 1940; MS025.006.004.003.00003 (Box MS025 Shared 2)
      Concerns Edward R. Murrow's salary increase, Christmas gift and future prospects at CBS
    - Correspondence - Rock, Vincent P., 1965; MS025.006.004.003.00004 (Box MS025 Shared 2)
      Concerns Mr. Rock's draft paper, "World-Wide Television and National Interest"
  - Diaries, 1949 -- 1959; MS025.006.005; 1.1 Linear Feet
    This subseries consists of professional diaries from Murrow's years at CBS.
    - Perpetual Datebook, 1949; MS025.006.005.001.00001 (Box 1)
    - National Diary, 1950; MS025.006.005.001.00002 (Box 1)
    - National Diary, 1951; MS025.006.005.001.00003 (Box 1)
    - National Diary, 1952; MS025.006.005.001.00004 (Box 1)
    - National Diary, 1953; MS025.006.005.001.00005 (Box 1)
    - National Diary, 1954, MS025.006.005.001.00006 (Box 1)
    - National Diary, 1955; MS025.006.005.001.00007 (Box 1)
    - National Diary, 1956; MS025.006.005.001.00008 (Box 1)
    - National Diary, 1957; MS025.006.005.001.00009 (Box 1)
    - National Diary, 1958; MS025.006.005.001.00010 (Box 1)
    - National Diary, 1959; MS025.006.005.001.00011 (Box 1)
    - Edward R. Murrow's Diary, 1957; MS025.006.005.002.00001 (Box 2)
      "Edward R. Murrow's 1957 Diary" written on the envelope containing this item. 39090011518392.
  - Scripts, 1938 -- 1961; MS025.006.006; 3.3 Linear Feet
    This subseries consists of selected, bound scripts from Edward R. Murrow's programs. See note on 'Selected Scripts.'
    - Crisis: September 1938. CBS Broadcasts of the Czechoslovakian Crisis, V.1, MS025.006.006.001.00001 (Box 1)
    - Crisis: September 1938. CBS Broadcasts of the Czechoslovakian Crisis, V.2, MS025.006.006.001.00002 (Box 1)
    - Crisis: September 1938. CBS Broadcasts of the Czechoslovakian Crisis, V.3, MS025.006.006.001.00003 (Box 1)
    - Crisis: September 1938. CBS Broadcasts of the Czechoslovakian Crisis, V.4, MS025.006.006.001.00004 (Box 1)
    - Crisis: September 1938. CBS Broadcasts of the Czechoslovakian Crisis, V.5, MS025.006.006.001.00005 (Box 1)
    - Crisis: September 1938. CBS Broadcasts of the Czechoslovakian Crisis, V.6, MS025.006.006.001.00006 (Box 1)
    - Crisis: September 1938. CBS Broadcasts of the Czechoslovakian Crisis, V.7, MS025.006.006.002.00001 (Box 2)
    - Crisis: September 1938. CBS Broadcasts of the Czechoslovakian Crisis, V.8, MS025.006.006.002.00002 (Box 2)
    - Crisis: September 1938. CBS Broadcasts of the Czechoslovakian Crisis, V.9, MS025.006.006.002.00003 (Box 2)
    - Crisis: September 1938. CBS Broadcasts of the Czechoslovakian Crisis, V.10, MS025.006.006.002.00004 (Box 2)
    - Person to Person, Vol. 1, No. 1, 1953 -- 1954; MS025.006.006.003.00001 (Box 3)
    - Person to Person, Vol. 1, No. 2, 1954; MS025.006.006.003.00002 (Box 3)
    - Person to Person, Vol. 2, No. 1, 1954 -- 1955; MS025.006.006.003.00003 (Box 3)
    - Person to Person, Vol. 2, No. 2, 1955; MS025.006.006.003.00004 (Box 3)
    - Person to Person, Vol. 3, No. 1, 1955 -- 1956; MS025.006.006.003.00005 (Box 3)
    - Person to Person, Vol. 3, No. 2, 1956; MS025.006.006.004.00001 (Box 4)
    - Person to Person, Vol. 4, No.1, 1956 -- 1957; MS025.006.006.004.00002 (Box 4)
    - Person to Person, Vol. 4, No. 2, 1957; MS025.006.006.004.00003 (Box 4)
    - Person to Person, Vol. 6, No. 1, 1958 -- 1959; MS025.006.006.004.00004 (Box 4)
    - Person to Person, Vol. 6, No. 2, 1959; MS025.006.006.004.00005 (Box 4)
    - Selected Murrow Scripts, 1938 -- 1950; MS025.006.006.005.00001 (Box 5)
      Note by Susanne Belovari, February 13, 2007: these scripts were collated later on, at least as late as Murrow's time at the USIA or even after his death. See here the introduction of the script from February 9, 1951 which talks about Murrow's work for the USIA. Scripts are introduced by an anonymous commentor. Texts were retyped for this compilation: they lack all editing marks by Murrow. Select pages were replaced by inserting pages of different paper quality, lines are replaced by ' ... ' It is impossible to ascertain how closely these retroactive compilations reflect original scripts and what was broadcast on the radio unless one compares each compiled script with original scripts and broadcasts when available. Also included are scripts not aired. Also included are scripts not aired.
    - Selected Murrow Scripts, 1950 -- 1952; MS025.006.006.005.00002 (Box 5)
      Note by Susanne Belovari, February 13, 2007: these scripts were collated later on, at least as late as Murrow's time at the USIA or even after his death. See here the introduction of the script from February 9, 1951 which talks about Murrow's work for the USIA. Scripts are introduced by an anonymous commentator. Texts were retyped for this compilation: they lack all editing marks by Murrow. Select pages were replaced by inserting pages of different paper quality, lines are replaced by ' ... ' It is impossible to ascertain how closely these retroactive compilations reflect the original scripts and what was broadcast originally on the radio unless one compares each compiled script with original scripts and broadcasts when available. Also included are scripts not aired. Also included are scripts not aired.
    - Selected Murrow Scripts, 1953 -- 1961; MS025.006.006.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - McCarthy Files, 1934 -- 1962; MS025.006.007; 0.55 Linear Feet
    This subseries consists of correspondence and publications related to Murrow's "See It Now" episodes on Senator Joseph McCarthy
    - McCarthy Files, Correspondence, 1953 -- 1954; MS025.006.007.001.00001 (Box 1)
    - "The Senator & the Broadcaster" by Joe Wershba, MS025.006.007.001.00002 (Box 1)
    - Publications about Senator Joseph McCarthy, 1951 -- 1962; MS025.006.007.001.00003 (Box 1)
    - Newspaper Clippings concerning Senator Joseph McCarthy, 1934 -- 1954; MS025.006.007.001.00004 (Box 1)
      There is duplicate copy of New Republic, March 30, 1953
    - Matter of "M" - Memorandum. Memo from D.H. Rivkin, 1954; MS025.006.007.001.00005 (Box 1)
      All other Matter of "M" files, see MS025/003.002.17. For all Matter of "M" Memoranda, see MS025/003.002.17 112:388
  - Publications, 1935 -- 1964; MS025.006.008; 3.3 Linear Feet
    This subseries consists of those publications owned by Edward R. Murrow, but not included in the Murrow Library series (MS025/007).
    [Organization]This subseries is arranged chronologically, as well as by size. Oversized publications are located in boxes 5-6.
    - Madame Tussaud's exhibition. Official guide & catalogue., 1935; MS025.006.008.001.00001; Madame Tussaud's Waxworks. (Box 1)
      Madame Tussaud's Waxworks.
    - The American school of the air. Teacher's manual and classroom guide, 1937; MS025.006.008.001.00002; Johnson, Helen. (Box 1)
    - "It can now be revealed," more about British railways in peace and war., 1945; MS025.006.008.001.00003; British Railways Press Office. (Box 1)
      Special dedication to Edward R. Murrow inserted opposite title page which includes signatures for members of the Southern Railway of England.
    - Research and writings on training, conditioning, treatment of athletic injuries, and corrective work., 1947; MS025.006.008.001.00004; Bohm, Wilbur (Box 1)
      2 v. Inscripton on title page of both volumes: "With my compliments to Edward R. Murrow. Sincerely always, "Doe" Wilbur Bohm."
    - The George Polk case: report of the Overseas Writers of the special committee to inquire into the murder at Salonika, Greece, May 16, 1948, of Columbia Broadcasting System correspondent George Polk., 1949; MS025.006.008.001.00005; Overseas Writers (Box 1)
      Committee to Inquire into the Murder of George Polk. Letter from Walter Lippmann inserted at front flyleaf.
    - Bibliography of Thomas Reed Powell, 1949; MS025.006.008.001.00006.1 (Box 1)
    - Papers inserted at front flyleaf of Bibliography of Thomas Reed Powell, MS025.006.008.001.00006.2 (Box 1)
      7 papers
    - Royalty Illustrated., 1949; MS025.006.008.001.00007 (Box 1)
      V. 1.
    - State department employee loyalty investigation. Report of a subcommittee of the Committee on Foreign Relations pursuant to S. Res. 231. A resolution to investigate whether there are employees in the State Department disloyal to the United States, together with individual views of Senator Lodge., 1950; MS025.006.008.001.00008; U.S. Senate. 81st Congress, 2d Session (Box 1)
      Annotated.
    - The Army school catalog., 1951; MS025.006.008.001.00009; Department of the Army (Box 1)
      Department of the Army Pamphlet 20-21. Inscription on front cover: "From Ed Kirby. See Jan 3, 52 letter."
    - This is Ike; the picture story of the man., 1952; MS025.006.008.001.00010.1; Hicks, Wilson; Soule, Gardner (Box 1)
      1st ed.
    - Correspondence inserted in This Is Ike, 1951 -- 1952; MS025.006.008.001.00010.2 (Box 1)
      2 letters inserted: Correspondence to Winston Burdette, one letter from Floyd and Elizabeth Lampkin and the second letter from Sam.
    - The union of western Europe: illusion and reality, 1952; MS025.006.008.001.00011; Lowenstein, Karl (Box 1)
      Inscription on front cover: "With warmest regards, KL."
    - Red roads to Mandalay., 1953; MS025.006.008.001.00012; Manchester, William (Box 1)
    - London Calling: the overseas journal of the BBC., 1953; MS025.006.008.001.00013 (Box 1)
      This edition concerns the coronation of Queen Elizabeth II.
    - Superior Films, Inc., vs. Department of Education of the State of Ohio, Division of Film Censorship. Brief of the National Council on Freedom from Censorship, a committee of the American Civil Liberties Union, amicus curiae., 1953; MS025.006.008.002.00001; U.S. Supreme Court; Ernst, Morris L. (Box 2)
      Inscription on front cover: "Ed Murrow - Comments on press theories may [?]. MLE."
    - Political affairs., 1953; MS025.006.008.002.00002 (Box 2)
      Vol. XXXII, No. 10 / Vol. XXXII, No. 11.
    - Coronet., 1953; MS025.006.008.002.00003 (Box 2)
      V. 35, No. 2.
    - Catalog of the Jean Hersholt Collection of Hans Christian Andersen. Library of Congress. Washington, 1954., MS025.006.008.002.00004 (Box 2)
      Inscription on front flyleaf: "To Ed Murrow. Greetings from his [?]. Jean Hersholt. [June?] 1955."
    - The American way to jobs, peace, democracy., 1954; MS025.006.008.002.00005; Communist Party of the United States of America (Box 2)
    - Confidential Diary: European journey, 1955., MS025.006.008.002.00006; Shotwell, James T. (Box 2)
    - Network practices: memorandum supplementing statement of Frank Stanton, President, Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. Prepared for the Senate Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce., 1956; MS025.006.008.002.00007; Columbia Broadcasting System, inc. (Box 2)
    - A rhetorical study: the radio speaking of Edward R. Murrow., 1957; MS025.006.008.003.00001; Woolley, Thomas Russell Jr. (Box 3)
    - What the British think of us: a study of British hostility to America and Americans and its motivation, with recommendations for improving Anglo-American relations., 1958; MS025.006.008.003.00002; Bernays, Doris; Bernays, Edward L. (Box 3)
    - Rocket city USA., 1959; MS025.006.008.003.00003; Akens, David S. (Box 3)
    - Problems of the nuclear arms race., 1959; MS025.006.008.003.00004; Federation of American Scientists (Box 3)
    - Special assignment: controversial commentaries., 1960; MS025.006.008.004.00001; Della Malva, Joseph; WPBC (Radio station) (Box 4)
      Author's signature on title page.
    - The voice of Latin America - and its significance in today's world, 1960; MS025.006.008.004.00002; Benton, William (Box 4)
      William Benton's Latin American manuscript for the Britannica 1961 Yearbook.
    - Civil Rights Packet. Russian #97 & Polish #69., 1964; MS025.006.008.004.00003 (Box 4)
    - Science Information Personnel papers., 1960 -- 1961; MS025.006.008.004.00004 (Box 4)
      Note attached: "W.R.4-A-?"
    - From Philadelphia to Philadelphia, MS025.006.008.004.00005; Powell, Thomas Reed (Box 4)
      Reprinted from The American Political Science Review Vol. XXXII, No. 1, February, 1938.
    - How philosophers may be useful to society., MS025.006.008.004.00006; Powell, Thomas Reed (Box 4)
      Reprinted from The International Journal of Ethics, Vol. XXXI, April, 1921.
    - The faith and hope of an American., MS025.006.008.004.00007; Graham, Frank P. (Box 4)
    - Look Magazine. "Edward R. Murrow Picks .. The ten most unforgettable speeches of the last 15 years", 1949; MS025.006.008.005.00001 (Box 5)
      pp. 52-55.
    - Ameryka. America Illustrated (issues 13-24)., 1959 -- 1960; MS025.006.008.005.00002 (Box 5)
    - Ameryka. America Illustrated (issues 1-12)., 1960 -- 1961; MS025.006.008.006.00001 (Box 6)
    - Ameryka. "Edward R. Murrow: As American as Plum Pudding.", 1961; MS025.006.008.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Photostats, 1953 -- 1954; MS025.006.009; 0.55 Linear Feet
    This subseries consists of photostats primarily for "See It Now" episodes airing between December 1953 and March 1954.
    - Photostats, See It Now, 1953; MS025.006.009.001.00001 (Box 1)
    - Photostats, See It Now, 1954; MS025.006.009.001.00002 (Box 1)
    - Photostats, See It Now, 1954; MS025.006.009.001.00003 (Box 1)
    - Photostats, See It Now, 1954; MS025.006.009.001.00004 (Box 1)
    - Photostats, Daily Worker, 1954; MS025.006.009.001.00005 (Box 1)
- Books, 1890 -- 1974; MS025.007; 0.55 Linear Feet
  This series consists of the 1,687 monographs held in bookcases in the Murrow Room at Fletcher.
  - Power and diplomacy., 1958; MS025.007.MR.00001; Acheson, Dean, 1893-1971. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    The Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, Tufts University, Medford, Mass. Back inside flap: Parts of this book were delivered by Mr. Acheson as the first annual William L. Clayton lectures at the Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy of Tufts University.
  - The epic of America., 1940; MS025.007.MR.00002; Adams, James Truslow, 1878-1949. (Box data_value_missing_5751afb2d5277595dfbddcb4991a143a)
    Inscription on front flyleaf: Janet Murrow. Handwritten note on inside of front flap: Highways of Progress.